# Steven Bi

## **Full-Stack Developer**

Perth WA steven.bb.0221@gmail.com 0450980608

Qualified software engineer, experiences in coding Js, Python and core Java, passionate about web app development with React/Django ecosystem, good on web based data visualization and API development. Familiar with Docker, Git dev environment as well as knowledge of deploy to AWS/GCP.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

#### Personal Details

Eligible to work in Australia: Yes

Highest Level of Education: Bachelor Degree

# Work Experience

## **Software Developer**

Atomorphis - Perth WA November 2020 to Present

Working on a primary in house product Gemini as well as maintain other exist products.

- Front-End implement, including dashboard UI, interactive geological map and data visualization
- Design and help in data visualization of minging fleet and equipment simulation in 2D & 3D
- API development
- Dockerize front-end sytem

### Web developer

South Pacific Union Group - Bunbury WA February 2020 to May 2020

Short contract with a local chain hotel in Bunbury, resolve current hotel website issues as well as maintain IT devices.

- Restore website from the damaged backup
- Restore online booking system
- Web based mail marketing system

### **Software Developer**

Lianjia (https://sh.lianjia.com/) - Shang Hai March 2019 to October 2019

- Maintain current web app
- Develop new features and design test cases

#### **BI Developer**

PinYi Information & Technology Co., Ltd (http://www.shpy.com) - Shang Hai June 2010 to April 2012

- 6 months intership, including knowledge of BI in banking, database and ETL tools training
- Offer consulting services for Bank of Communications
- Data migrate & analysis & maintain for Bank of Communications

#### Education

## **Bachelor of Science (Computing) in Software Engineering**

Curtin University - Perth WA

August 2014 to December 2018

### Skills

- Python (2 years)
- Django (1 year)
- Pyxll (Less than 1 year)
- Node js (2 years)
- React (2 years)
- Java (2 years)
- Docker (1 year)
- Deck.gl (2 years)
- Html (2 years)
- Css (2 years)
- JS (2 years)
- Git (2 years)

#### Links

https://chen-bbe.github.io/MyPage/

https://github.com/Chen-BBe/

# Certifications and Licenses

**SCJP** 2010 to 2012

Sun Certified Java Programmer

# Additional Information

• Language: Mandarin and English